Guide to the John Eugene Unterecker Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VIII: Correspondence files
  - Rack, Allan
  - Radell, Karen
  - Rago, Henry -- poet, editor
  - Rajan, B. -- critic
  - Rakosi, Karl -- poet
  - Ramerez, Tino
  - Ramesh, Suda
  - Ramanujan, A.K.
  - Ran, Raja
  - Rankin, Dot
  - Rankin, William
  - Rapp, Elaine
  - Ratner, Rochelle
  - Ravindranath, P.
  - Ray, David
  - Ray, Gordon
  - Rayson, Ann
  - Reardon, Dan -- Irish poet
  - Redmond, Michael
  - Redpath, Kim
  - Regier, W.G.
  - Reidy, M.J.
  - Reisner, Bill
  - Rendell, Marion
  - Reporter, The
  - Reuman, Bob
  - Revel, Pam
  - Rhodes, Robert E
  - Rhodes, Willard (Box 37.)
  - Rich, Fay
  - Richardson, Ethel
  - Richardson, Harold
  - Richardson, Serena
  - Ricketts, Wendell
  - Ridgely, Joe
  - Riggins, Denise
  - Ritter, Blake
  - Ritter, Chris
  - Rittgers, Carol
  - Riviere, Gladys
  - Roach, Marguerite
  - Robbins, Raymond
  - Roberts, Cheri
  - Roberts, Lo
  - Robinson, Barbara
  - Rodino, Sal
  - Rodriguez, Tino
  - Roggenbuck, Peggy
  - Roman, Mike
  - Rosenberg, John
  - Rosenberg, Ruth
  - Rosenblum, Irwin
  - Rosenthal, lewis
  - Rosenthal, Mack -- critic
  - Rosset, Barney
  - Rossi, Joe
  - Rossman, Charles
  - Roston, Bill
  - Roston, Mary Ann
  - Rosenthal, Lewis
  - Rowland, Stanley
  - Rubens, Janet
  - Rubicon
  - Rubin, Lawrence
  - Ruby, Laura
  - Ruddick, Peter
  - Rudman, Mark -- poet -- two folders
  - Ruppenthal, Sarah
  - Rutgers University Press
  - Ruthenberg, Irene
  - Ryan, Maybelle
  - Ryan, Rita and Jim
  - Ryan, William F.
  - Sachiko
  - Sadoff, Ira (Box 38)
  - Sage, Ann
  - Saiki, Arnold
  - Saint John, David
  - St. Omer, Garth
  - Saito, Gary
  - Salah, Muhammed
  - Salazar, Owana (Theresa)
  - Salmagundi
  - Samarin, Tatiana
  - Sanasardo, Paul
  - Sandler, Natalie
  - Sanford, Charles
  - Sanford, Richard
  - San Francisco Ballet
  - Sarot, Ellin
  - Sasa, Yasuki
  - Saturday Review
  - Sauers, Ann
  - Schaffner, Jordan
  - Schechner, Dick -- two folders (Box 39)
  - Scherer, William
  - Schiller, Daniel H.
  - Schlieman, Ernest
  - Schlossberg, Edwin
  - Schneider, Susan
  - Schoch, Russell, Jr.
  - Schoenberg, Gina
  - Schott, Webster
  - Schramm, Darrell
  - Schrayer, Paula
  - Schreiber, Ron
  - Schwab, Arnold
  - Schwaber, Paul
  - Schwall, Hedwig
  - Scwartz, Julie
  - Schwartz, Lloyd
  - Scribner's (American Writers)
  - Sears, Michael
  - Segessman, Harry
  - Seidman, Hugh
  - Shaffer, Susan Fromberg
  - Shalit, Nancy and Gene (Box 40)
  - Shalit, Peter
  - Shapiro, Alan
  - Shapiro, Cecile
  - Shapiro, David -- poet and critic
  - Sharma, Maya
  - Sharpe, William
  - Sharrad, Paul
  - Shaugnessy, Joseph R.
  - Sheaffer, Louis
  - Sheehy, Eugene
  - Sheldon, Paul
  - Shenandoah
  - Sherry, Ruth
  - Sherwin, Judith Johnson
  - Shi, David E.
  - Shiffert, Edith
  - Shigekane, Lydia
  - Shimer, Dorothy
  - Shinoda, Elizabeth
  - Shinto, Patty
  - Shiraishi, Kazuko
  - Shiroma, Yumi
  - Shoeuberger, Cindy
  - Shore, Jane -- poet
  - Sharader, Steve
  - Sibley, Gay
  - Sicks, Laurel
  - Siegel, David N.
  - Signpost Press
  - Silbert, Layle
  - Silbey, Dorothy
  - Silverman, Rita
  - Silverman, Stuart
  - Silverstein, Norm
  - Simboli, Ray
  - Simon, Marjorie
  - Simone, Albert
  - Simons, Paul
  - Simpson, Eileen
  - Simpson, Gene
  - Simpson, George
  - Sinclair, Marjorie
  - Sisskin, Sylvia
  - Skarda
  - Skeeter, Sharyn
  - Skellings, Edmund
  - Skinner, Michelle
  - Slang (Box 41)
  - Slater, Kay
  - Sligo
  - Slow Loris Press
  - Smallwood, Randy
  - Smith, Carolyn
  - Smith, Harry
  - Smith, John E.
  - Smith, K.
  - Smith, Louise
  - Smith, Pamela F.
  - Smith, Stewart
  - Smith, Terry
  - Smoller, Eleanor
  - Sneidman, Ernest
  - Snow, Frank
  - Sobin, Tony
  - Social Security Information
  - Sodetoni, Wendy
  - Sokol
  - Soldo, John
  - Solomon, hyde
  - Solomon, Margaret
  - Solotaroff, Theodore -- fiction writer, editor
  - Sommer, Hollis
  - Sommers, Mary
  - Song, Cathy -- poet
  - Sorrell, Kathy (Box 42)
  - South, Karen
  - Sothern Illinois University Press
  - Southern Poetry Review
  - Southern Review
  - Spalding, Phyllis
  - Spanier, Sheryl
  - Spears, M.K.
  - Spigelmire, Lynne
  - Spring Church Book Company
  - Stade, George
  - Stadler, Quandra
  - Stafford, William
  - Stahl, Ellen
  - Stanford, Ann
  - Stanford, Don
  - Stap, Don
  - State Foundation on Culture and the Arts
  - Staton, Shirley
  - Steele, John A.
  - Stein, Bill
  - Steppenwolf
  - Sternberg, Linda
  - Sternberg, martin
  - Stevenson, Janet
  - Stewart, Frank -- poet
  - Stewart, Liane
  - Stewart, Susan
  - Stifler, Lisa
  - Stimpson, Catharine
  - Stimson, R.J.
  - Stock, Doreen
  - Stoehr, Taylor
  - Stolen Paper Review
  - Stoner, Donna
  - Stoops, Albert
  - Stout, Rex
  - Strack, Ellie
  - Srand, karin
  - Stratton, Sandy
  - Straus, Roger III
  - Strauss, Irene
  - Stuart, Dabney -- poet
  - Sturman, Janet
  - Suey Ping Toy
  - Sugg, Richard
  - Suh Kook Young
  - Suiso, Dot
  - Sullivan, Cathy
  - Sullivan, Charles
  - Sullivan, John
  - Sullivan, Nancy
  - Sulloway, Alison
  - Sumida, Steve
  - Summers, Hollis
  - Summersgill, Travis
  - Sundial
  - Surman, Diana
  - Susskind, Harriet
  - Susskind, Lawrence
  - Suther, Marshall
  - Sutherland, Audrey (Box 43)
  - Sutherland, Edwin
  - Sutherland, Walton
  - Swarthmore College
  - Swift, Dave
  - Szatrowski, Mrs. Z.T.
  - Szerlip, Barbara
  - Tabachnick, Anne
  - Tachiyama, Gary
  - Tael, Thomas
  - Takahara, Mel (2 folders)
  - Takayesu, Lori
  - Takete, Eddie
  - Talerico, Victor
  - Talpey, Tom
  - Tamanaha, Susan
  - Tamminga, Susan
  - Tamplin, R.N.J.
  - Tandy, Keith
  - Tannler, Robert
  - TAO Fraternity
  - Tardif, Henry
  - Tarrant, Warren
  - Tashima, Margaret
  - Tate, James -- poet
  - Tave, Stuart M.
  - Tavis, Thaumas
  - Tayler, Edward
  - Taylor, Andrew
  - Taylor, Brian
  - Taylor, Davidson
  - Taylor, Pat
  - Taylor, Ruie
  - Teller, Walter (Box 44)
  - Tendril
  - Tennent, Val
  - Tennessee Poetry Journal
  - Terada, Vinnie
  - Tew, Arnold G.
  - Thicket
  - Thiesen, Leonard
  - Things
  - This Issue
  - Thomas, Brook
  - Thomas, Debra
  - Thomas, Selden
  - Thomas, Tael
  - Thompson, April
  - Thompson, Phyllis (2 folders)
  - Thurber, Lona Louise
  - Thurley, Geoffrey
  - Tierney, R.
  - Titus, Mary (Box 45)
  - Todd, Ann Togawa
  - Tomeika, Ariel
  - Tomich, Margot
  - Toner, Tim
  - Townley, Marti
  - Tracey, Billy T.
  - Transatlantic Review
  - Tranter, John -- poet
  - Triad
  - Tribble, Keith
  - Tripoli, Mary Elizabeth
  - Tripp, Ed
  - Tri-Quarterly
  - Truitt, Anne
  - Truman, David
  - Tsujimoto, Joel
  - Tulloch, Graham
  - Turkel, Barbara
  - Turner, Dorothy
  - Twigg-Smith, Benedict
  - Twitty, Grace
  - Uchiyama, Kent
  - Ullman, Joseph M.
  - Unger, Leonard
  - University of California Press
  - University of Chicago Press
  - University of Colorado at Boulder
  - University of Hawaii
  - University of Illinois at Urbana- Champaign
  - University of Kansas City Review
  - University of Missouri Press
  - University of North Carolina Press
  - University of Pennsylvania Press
  - University of Pittsburgh Press
  - University of South Carolina
  - University of Texas
  - University of Texas Press
  - University of Wisconsin Press
  - University Press of Hawaii
  - University Press of Kansas
  - Ushinoda, Cheryl
  - Van Brunt, Lloyd -- poet
  - Van de Vate, Nancy
  - Van Duyn, Mona
  - Van Dyke, Vanessa
  - Van Niel, Robert
  - Vanture, Raul
  - Van Zile, Judy
  - Vardamis, Alex
  - Vas Dias, Robert
  - Venit, Jim
  - Verdy, Violette
  - Vetere, Richard
  - Vial, Connie
  - Village Voice
  - Vintage Books Correspondence
  - Vinz, Mark
  - Virginia Quarterly Review
  - Vitacco, Pat
  - Voelcker, Hunce
  - Vogelsang, Arthur (Box 46)
  - Voices
  - Volcano Art Center
  - Volkert, Epie
  - Volpe, Ed
  - Von-Garske, Elizabeth
  - Von Manowski, Heather
  - Voshell, Marilyn Jill
  - Voyages
  - Wagner, Linda
  - Wagoner, David
  - Walck, Inc.
  - Waldhorn, Arthur
  - Walken, Glen
  - Walker, Lawrence
  - Walker, Virginia
  - Wallace, Robert
  - Walsh, Chad
  - Walters, Lynn
  - Waltman, Howard
  - Walz, Mary
  - Wang, Arthur W.
  - Ward, Charles
  - Ward, Susan
  - Warren, Fred and Lee
  - Waters, Rick
  - Wayne State University
  - Wayne, Valery
  - Weales, Gerald
  - Webb, Muffie
  - Webster, Brenda
  - Wechter, Marie
  - Weems, Ben
  - Weil, James
  - Weiner, Deborah
  - Weisberg, Robert
  - Weiss, Elaine
  - Weiss, Flo
  - Weiss, Rene and Ted
  - Welish, Marjorie -- poet
  - Wendroff, William
  - Wendt, Albert
  - Wensberg, Eric
  - Wentworth, Richard
  - Werbow, Stanley
  - Werner, R.J.
  - Werthamer, Cynthia
  - Wesleyan University Press
  - West Point
  - Westen, Flora
  - Western Humanities Review
  - Westigan Review
  - Westlake, Wayne
  - Westler, Max Jay (Box 47)
  - Weston, John
  - Weston, Susan
  - Wetterau, John
  - Wexler, Max
  - White, Robert
  - White, Ron
  - Whiteside, George
  - Who's Who
  - Whitford, Josephine
  - Whittemore, Reed
  - Who's Who in Poetry in American Colleges and Universities
  - Widner, Jill
  - Wiehler, Hans
  - Wiggins, Henry H.
  - Wilderness Letters
  - Wilderness Society
  - Williams, Bob
  - Williams, Elizabeth
  - Williams, Galen
  - Williams, Harrison
  - Williams, John
  - Williams, Kathryn
  - Williams, Norma
  - Williamson, Anne
  - Wills
  - Wilson, Craig
  - Wilson, Frank
  - Wilson, Mark
  - Wilson, Richard
  - Wilson, Rob -- poet
  - Wimmer, Dick
  - Wind
  - Winsor, William
  - Winters, Ann -- poet
  - Winters, Lee
  - Wirtzen, Jim (Box 48)
  - Wise, James N.
  - Wise, Kelly
  - Wise, Louis
  - Wiseman, Joseph
  - Wohlgelernter, Maurice
  - Wolkenfield, Jack
  - Wong May
  - Wong, Michael
  - Wong, Suzanne
  - Wood, Kathy
  - Wood, Susan
  - Wood, Susanne
  - Woodring, Carl
  - Wormwood Review
  - Worth, Douglas
  - Wray, Jeanne Adams
  - Wright, Dorothy
  - Wright, Mary
  - Wyatt, Kenneth F.
  - Wykes, Patricia
  - Wyrtzer, Jim
  - Yaddo
  - Yale Review
  - Yale University Press
  - Yamada, Calvin
  - Yamada, Gail
  - Yamada, Leona
  - Yamanaka, Sachiko (Box 49)
  - Yamamoto, Don
  - Yamashita, Don
  - Yankee Magazine
  - Yanovsky, Isabella
  - Yeager, J.L.
  - Yeats International Summer School
  - Yeats, Mrs. W.B.
  - Yim, Susan
  - YMHA
  - Yokota, Michiko
  - Yonezaki, Ann
  - Yoshikawa, Terry
  - Yoshimira, Wesley
  - Young, George
  - Young, Virginia
  - Youngblood, Michael
  - Yuson, Alfred
  - Zappia, Steve
  - Zavatsky, Bill
  - Zeck, Gregory
  - Zimroth, Evan
  - Zucaro, Michael
  - Zuckerman, H.
  - Zugay, Sharon
  - Zwerdling, Alex
- Series IX: Poetry Manuscripts
  - Abelard Perhaps and Perhaps Heloise (Box 50)
  - Accept
  - Address to the Beast of the Fable
  - Adventures in Star Travel
  - Afternoons
  - After the Birthday
  - After Three Years We Meet ...
  - Age 12
  - Album
  - Albumn
  - All These Sunsets
  - Ampurias, Spain
  - Anemones of Collioure
  - Animals, The
  - Anniversaries, Birthdays, Saints' Day
  - Anthem
  - Anti-Ghazal
  - Apology of midnight
  - Aprils
  - Arroyo: Flash Flood
  - At Renvyle
  - At the Edge
  - At the Rim of the Caldera
  - Atoll
  - Aubade of Sorts
  - August 22
  - Bartok Quartet
  - Bas-relief at Banyuls
  - Beach
  - Before Dawn
  - Beginnings (The Garden, The Apple, The Birth)
  - Below Decks
  - Below the Cliffs, Donegal
  - Bent Light
  - Betrayal, The
  - Birthday Poem (Dec. 29)
  - Birthday Poem (Jan. 17)
  - Blues for Two Voices
  - Bridge: Sligo
  - Brisk Afternoons
  - Bruises
  - Burn, The
  - By Fire (Box 51)
    [Formerly Anti-Ghazal]
  - Cabinet Meeting
  - Calendar Hymn
  - Calliandra Inaequilatera Rusby
  - Cameras
  - Canadian Summer: 1933
  - Canrnival at Amelie-les-Bains
  - Carrowkeel
  - Case for the Limited War
  - Catalan Farmer: Figueras, Spain
  - Caught
  - Caves, The
  - Celebratory Song to be Sung Halfway Through the Annual Spring Faculty Dance
  - Chain Poems
  - Cities
  - Citizen of Another Climate
  - City Winter
  - Climbing: Ireland
  - Coastline
  - Cold's Three Visits
  - Collioure Afternoon
  - Collioure Wisteria
  - Configuration
  - Construction in Five Stanzas
  - Counterpoint for Tenor, Contralto, and Cymbals
  - Cross-Country
  - Dancers, The
  - Dark Song
  - Darke Theatre, The
  - Dark Vineyard, The (Box 52)
  - December Event
  - December Snowstorm
  - Definition, The
  - Dialogue in February
  - Dialogue in November
  - Dialogue in Winter
  - Discarded Typewriter Ribbon: Writing Seminar: Maile Leaves
  - Discoveries, As Under Floodlights
  - Dolphin
  - Dream Window
  - Dreams
  - Dublin Evening: Afternoon Near Clifden
  - Edge (Coastline)
  - Elmwood Avenue...
  - End of Winter
  - Endings
  - English 3 (1938)
  - Envelope, The
  - Ephemeris for a Dark Time
  - Equinox
  - Erotic Poem #1
  - Evening: All of Our Sad Violins
  - Event
  - Exile
  - Explorer
  - Faces, The
  - Fall, The
  - Falling
  - Family
  - Fathers
  - Festival
  - Field/Wind/Cinder
  - First Trip to the Fun House in Crystal Beach
  - Fish
  - Five Cattle in an Evening Meadow
  - Five-Forty-two A.M.: Their Presence
  - Flickerings (Box 53)
  - Flight Letter
  - For Julia
  - For M.H. Nicolson
  - Founds
  - Four Short Blunders From Beneath the Alogical Bus
  - Four Meditations From the Middle Ages
  - Fragments From an Autumn Journal
  - Fragments in the Form of an IOU
  - Friends, Lovers, at Pohoiki, Hawaii
  - Garden, The
  - Genesis
  - Get Lost, He Said
  - Getting Old
  - Ghana Evening With Three Friends...
  - Gift, The
  - Grafton Landscape
  - Groups of Five
  - Guardian
  - Guavas
  - Gunsight
  - Han Dynasty
  - Harbor
  - Hawaii, Near Apua Point
  - Hero, The
  - Honolulu Zoo: October (Box 54)
  - Horoscope
  - Horses
  - Hospital: Post-Operative: 3
  - Hotels
  - I-Spy
  - In Five Minutes
  - In the Next Room
  - In the Studio
  - Indian Summer Midnight
  - Inhabitant
  - Interlude
  - Interlude at Eden
  - Interval
  - Interview
  - Invasion, The
  - Invention With Young Figures on a Dark Landscape
  - Invitation, The
  - Irish Winter
  - Island
  - Island in Autumn, The
  - Italian Sonnet...
  - January
  - January Crossing
  - January Fragment
  - January Invasions
  - January 23: Fragment
  - Joan of Arc Revisited
  - Journey
  - Kai's Sandcastle
  - Kitchen
  - Knotted Image
  - Lady and the Mortician, The Lake
  - Landscape With Cat and Dragonfly...
  - Landscape With Tall Figures Walking
  - Landscapes
  - Language Barrier in Mexico City (Box 55)
  - Late
  - Lava
  - Lavatures
  - Letter From the Pier
  - Letter: October
  - Letter to a Firend's Loneliness
  - Lines for Ranchless Erik Wensberg
  - Listening to the Night
  - Long Afternoon, The
  - Long Distance
  - Long Light at Evening
  - Losses
  - Luxurious Seasons, The
  - March Landscape
  - Meditation on the Word
  - Message
  - Middle Ages, The
  - Midnight Geometry
  - Midnight Guava
  - Midnight Signature
  - Midnight Telephone...
  - Mid-Winter
  - Monumental Dancer
  - Morning
  - Morning Song
  - Mrs. Lutcher's Parrot
  - Muse, The (Box 56)
  - Natural History
  - Navigator
  - Nearly Anonymous Figure...
  - Neither Hamlet, Laertes, Ophelia, Nor Horatio
  - New Bridge, The
  - Night
  - Night Letter
  - Night Piece
  - Nocturne
  - North of Collioure...
  - Not Going to the Reservation
  - Not Photographing James Wright as Santa Claus
  - Not Quite the Sun, Not Quite the Moon
  - Not Swimming Below the Cliff
  - Nothing Soft, Nothing Loved
  - November Changing
  - Now
  - Number 16: Plage a Trouville
  - Nursery Song
  - Oahu: Mid-day Concert in Orange Air
  - Obake Song
  - Objects and Persons in the Room, The (Box 57)
  - October
  - Offhand Jazz from the Concert Hall
  - Opening Out -- For Stephanie Hicks Craib
  - Orations
  - Papayas, The
  - Passage
  - Passenger
  - Paul Fields, Summer, 1948
  - Pennsylvania Summer
  - Phaedra
  - Phew
  - Photographs
  - Physical
  - Poem (These Certain Things)
  - Poem for George in June 1988
  - Poem for George Weinheimer
  - Poem for Karen on August 29
  - Poem for Liam Miller, A
  - Poem in July
  - Points of View
  - Political Poem
  - Political Sonnet: The Werewolf
  - Political Statement
  - Porch
  - Portrait
  - Portraits, The
  - Praise
  - Prayer for the Lion, the Elk, the Bear, the Mole
  - Preparing the Seed Bed
  - Privacies
  - Problem in Construction
  - Process
  - Project for Autumn, A
  - Projection
  - Prospect of Five-Month-Old Females Awash
  - Public Lecture (Box 58)
  - Quintet
  - Ragged Autumn
  - Rain Portrait
  - Reconstruction
  - Red Coat
  - Red Door
  - Rehearsals
  - Remembered Streetriders
  - Renewals
  - Return, The
  - Revisions: 1968
  - Rival
  - River: High Places
  - Rivers Is Stained, The...
  - River Song
  - Rivers, Roads, Blood Vessels
  - Roof, The
  - Room, The
  - Ruined Bridge Seen From a Plane
  - Rust-Colored Shirt, The
  - Sail, The
  - Sanderling
  - Scientist
  - Script
  - Scrub Peach Near Volcano, Hawaii: January
  - Search
  - Self-conscious Historian, The
  - Separate
  - September's Child
  - Shoreline
  - Six Twenty-six P.M.
  - Sleepers
  - Sleepless
  - Sodom
  - Song at drumholm
  - Song at End of Winter
  - Song for Denise, for Jolie, for Christie
  - Song for Emily
  - Song of the Giant of the Weather
  - Songs. (Box 59)
  - Souterrain
  - Spanish Landscape
  - Spring Break-up
  - Stab at the Truth (Trying for Lost Darkness)
  - Start
  - Statement "I"
  - Statement "II"
  - Stevador
  - Still Life
  - Still Life: Hawaii
  - Still Life With Apple, Banana, and Two Guavas
  - Stone, The
  - Stone Beach: Connemara
  - Stone Burial
  - Stone of Ampurial, The
  - Stones at the Bottom of the Toy Box
  - Summer (Box 60)
  - Summer Fragment
  - Sunday Schools
  - Swallows, the Windows, The
  - Swan Lake
  - Talking to the Darkness
  - Taste Like Salt; Brightness Like the Sea, A
  - Test, The
  - Thief
  - Thoughts on the Dissolution of the 11-year-old Tindall/Unterecker Seminar
  - Three
  - Three Figures on a Summer Landscape
  - Three Gratitudes and One Invocation from the Annual Midwinter Family Tea
  - Three Pessimistic Poems
  - Three Rhymes for Everybody's Nursery
  - Three Short Poems Having to Do With Darkness
  - Tir Connaill
  - To John Donne
  - Torque
  - Toward
  - Toward Madeloc
  - Toward Morning
  - Transcript
  - Transformation
  - Travellers
  - True Waltz
  - Two Islands
  - Two Meditations From the Middle Ages
  - Two Trains (Noel Callow, Leaving)
  - Ulla Start, Spain
  - Unicorn Tapestry, The
  - Unidentified
  - Uninvited
  - Union Choir Service: Pennsylvania, June 22
  - Use For Summer and a Use For Sand, A
  - Valley, The
  - Variations
  - Victory (Box 61)
  - Videotape: Eight Second Pause
  - Visit, The
  - Visitor
  - Volcano
  - Waiting
  - Warp
  - Washington Scene, The
  - Watchman
  - Waterfalls; Sea Arches; Roses
  - We Are In a Sea of Wild Flowers...
  - White Orchid
  - White Stone Beach, The
  - Who Let the Muzak Go Out of Our Mirage?
  - William Playing
  - Wind and Night Sky
  - Wind, Sky, and Sea
  - Wine
  - Winter Leaves (Box 62)
  - Winter Night
  - Winter Poem
  - Winter Statements
  - Winter Storm
  - Winter Trees at Aiea
  - Within.Into.Inside.Under.Within...
  - Word, The
  - Yellow Laundry Soap, The
- Series X: Other Manuscripts
  - Acting -- reviews (Box 62)
  - Addresses, records of publication, etc.
  - Addresses -- poetry
  - American Way -- ballet piece
  - American Way -- Hawaii piece
  - American Way -- photography and biography
  - American Way - poetry piece
  - American Way -- review (Bly, Wright, Orr)
  - American Way -- reviews
  - Anthology idea with Roger
  - Anthology Ideas (Jim Wise)
  - Article ideas and story ideas
  - Articles on my own poetry for Kentucky Poetry Review special issue
  - Articles
  - Articles -- The Architecture of the Bridge
  - Articles -- Evergreen Review
  - Articles -- "From Prison to Poetry" -- interview with Etheridge Knight
  - Article -- The President's Column -- Gloxina News
  - Articles -- Gloxina Society Columns
  - Articles -- HLAC Newsletter pieces
  - Article in Middlebury Campus -- 7/14/43
  - Article -- Ezra Pound encyclopedia piece (Harper's) 1974
  - Article -- tour
  - Article -- Yeats - New York Times
  - Auden as American
  - Biographical Statement -- Jack Unterecker
  - Bishop, Elizabeth (Box 63)
  - Blurbs
  - Book mss. -- Conarroe Berryman
  - Book mss. -- Nelson Bly
  - Book mss. -- Orr Bly
  - Book mss. -- Kidder Cummings (Box 64)
  - Book mss. -- Dance Sequence draft
  - Book mss. -- Dance Sequence ms. revisions
  - Book mss. -- Dance Sequence
  - Book mss. -- Dance Sequence -- publisher's copies and dominion
  - Book mss. -- Dance Sequence -- uncut
  - Book mss. -- Dance Sequence -- complete ms.
  - Book mss. -- Dark Vineyards, The
  - Book mss. -- Dark Vineyards (Box 65)
  - Book mss. -- Dark Vineyards
  - Book mss. -- Dreaming Zoo, A
  - Book mss. -- Fifty-one Doors
  - Book mss. -- Forms of Modern British Fiction
  - Book mss. - -Hawaii anthology
  - Book mss. -- tentative Hawaii book
  - Book mss. -- I Learn By Going -- Heriman
  - Book mss. -- Hughes -- Onwachekwa Jemie
  - Book mss. -- Lowell -- Rudman (Box 66)
  - Book mss. - -Merrill -- Moffett
  - Book mss. - -Objects and Persons in the Room, The
  - Book mss. -- Objects -- deletions and revisions
  - Book mss. -- Objects -- exclusions from (Box 67)
  - Book mss. -- Objects -- draft ms.
  - Book mss. -- Objects -- original drafts
  - Book mss. -- Orr, Gregory - new book ms.
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii -- drafts
  - Book mss. -- Poems of Living Hawaii -- accepted group
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii -- records
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii -- Typescript (Box 68)
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii -- early version
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii -- preface
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii -- promotional meterial
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii -- Shoreline
  - Book mss. -- Poetry Hawaii -- short version
  - Book mss. -- Start-- original ms.
  - Book mss. -- Start
  - Book mss.-- Stone-- first page proofs
  - Book mss.--Stone
  - Book mss.-- Stone- early draft
  - Book mss.--Stone-- early draft -- incomplete
  - Book mss.-- Stone-- ms. and permissons
  - Book mss. -- Stone -- ms. (Box 69)
  - Book mss. -- Stone ms, revisions
  - Book mss. -- Stone -- ms.
  - Book mss. -- Study of the Function..., A
  - Book mss. - Those Dying Generations (2 bound mss.)
  - Book mss. -- Use for Summer and a Use for Sand, A
  - Book mss. -- Use -- bound ms. (Box 70)
  - Book mss. -- When the Winds Blow
  - Book mss. -- Who Let the Music...
  - Book mss. -- Yeats and Patrick McCartan -- 2 folders
  - Book mss. -- Yeats -- drafts
  - Book mss. -- Yeats: Twentieth Century Views
  - Book mss. -- Reader's Guide to W.B. Yeats
  - Contemporary Literary Criticism
  - Dissertation Notes -- Yeats
  - Drafts -- Bishop Ms.
  - Drafts -- Middle Ages, The
  - Drafts -- Introductions To Be Filed
  - Reader's Guide to W.B. Yeats Material
  - Durrell Ms -- Durrell Conference (Box 71)
  - Durrell Mss. -- Durrell, Lawrence, etc.
  - Durrell mss. -- Durrell conference
  - East-West Conference
  - Essay mss. -- Durrell and Beckett piece
  - Essay mss. -- Eliot
  - Essay mss. -- GMA first draft
  - Essay mss. -- "The Irish Peasant"
  - Essay mss. -- "Of Father, Of Son"
  - Essay mss. --"Putting Together of William Butler Yeats"
  - Essay mss. -- "Response" -- re. Durrell
  - Essay mss. -- "Shape-changing of Contemporary Poetry"
  - Essay mss. -- "Shaping Force in Yeats' Plays, The"
  - Essay mss. -- Special Issue of Voyages
  - Essay mss. -- Yeats and Patrick McCartan
  - Fiction Drafts (Box 72)
  - Fiction Inquest
  - Interview -- "To Kinnell, One's Self is One's Material"
  - Interview -- Liam Miller (two folders)
  - Modern British Anthology
  - National Book Award Citation
  - New York City Ballet book
  - Notes - Susanne Langer's Aesthetics class
  - Performance Poetry -- Concordium Hawaii